It costs more to have a highly available platform.
拥有一个高可用性平台的成本更高
You pass this cost through to your customers.
您将此成本传递给您的客户
Your customers likely don't use your platform 24 hours a day, every day.
您的客户可能不会每天 24 小时使用您的平台
What should we do then? Scheduled maintenance.
那怎么办呢 ? 已安排的维护
This can be a win-win.
这可以是双赢的
Do your customers care if your platform is up at 3:00 AM on a Saturday morning?
您的客户是否关心您的平台是否在周六 AM 3:00 起床 ?
They may, or depending on what service your platform offers, they may not.
他们可能 或者根据您的平台提供的服务 他们可能不会
If you and your customers can agree on certain times
如果您和您的客户可以在特定时间达成一致
of day or certain times of day on certain days,
在某一天的某一天或某一天的某一天
then you can build in scheduled maintenance.
那么您可以在预定的维护中进行构建
You can pass on some of that cost savings then to your customers.
您可以将这些成本节省的部分传递给客户
Scheduled maintenance is basically a free pass on downtime.
预定的维护基本上是停机时间的免费传递
If you agree that your platform can be down every
如果你同意你的平台可以
Sunday from 1:00 AM to 3:00 AM in a certain time zone,
周日 AM 1:00 至 AM 3:00 在某时区
then you have a time where you can take care of necessary changes to your platform.
那么您就有时间 您可以对平台进行必要的更改
This gives you the ability to more easily be up and running during normal business hours.
这使您能够更轻松地在正常工作时间内启动和运行
Thus, you can build
因此 您可以构建
a less complex and less costly system that meets your customers needs.
不那么复杂且成本较低的系统 满足您的客户需求
Do your customers need every aspect of your system
您的客户是否需要系统的各个方面
up and running perfectly to get value from your platform?
完美地从你的平台获取价值
It is possible that there are aspects that are not really required but are nice to haves.
可能有一些方面并不是真正需要的 但对我们来说是好的
If so, you can exclude these items from your SLA and make your up time task a bit easier.
如果是这样 您可以从 SLA 中排除这些项 并使您的上行时间任务变得更容易
Force majeure, force of nature or act of God are terms used to describe
不可抗力 自然力或神的行为是用来描述的术语
things that are beyond anyone's control or beyond any reasonable level of control.
超出任何人控制或超出任何合理控制范围的事情
This term is almost always included in a contract
此术语几乎总是包含在合同中
as coverage for extraordinary circumstances.
作为对特殊情况的报道
As we can see, downtime is not so simple.
我们可以看到 停机时间并不那么简单
Given all that we've talked about,
鉴于我们所谈论的一切
how do we determine downtime?
如何确定停机时间 ?
Always put serious thought and consideration into measuring
总是认真思考和考虑
your downtime and think about needs like maintenance windows.
您的停机时间 并考虑维护窗口之类的需求
Make sure that you know how to calculate
确保您知道如何计算
your downtime before a customer ask the question.
客户提出问题之前的停机时间
Make sure that the calculation is in writing,
确保计算以书面形式计算
includes all exclusions, and is referenced in any contracts that you have in place.
包含所有排除项 并且在您已执行的任何合同中引用